<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Paul-Razvan Sarbu</title>
    <link>https://sageata.github.io/portfolio/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Paul-Razvan Sarbu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Paul-Razvan Sarbu - All rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 11:39:16 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sageata.github.io/portfolio/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Recreating Apple&#39;s iOS Wallet Animations with Flutter and Dart</title>
      <link>https://sageata.github.io/portfolio/blog/004-flutter-animations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 11:39:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sageata.github.io/portfolio/blog/004-flutter-animations/</guid>
      <description>In the world of mobile development, animations can make or break user experience. Inspired by the sleek animations in Apple&amp;rsquo;s iOS Wallet, I embarked on a journey to replicate them using Flutter and Dart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better Forms</title>
      <link>https://sageata.github.io/portfolio/blog/005-isurvey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 11:39:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sageata.github.io/portfolio/blog/005-isurvey/</guid>
      <description>iSurvey In a world dominated by platforms like Survey Monkey, Qualtrics, and Microsoft Forms, each with its own strengths and weaknesses, there&amp;rsquo;s room for innovation. Enter iSurvey, a project designed to empower survey authors and enhance the data collection process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Six Sigma - Part Two</title>
      <link>https://sageata.github.io/portfolio/blog/007-six-sigma-part-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 11:39:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sageata.github.io/portfolio/blog/007-six-sigma-part-two/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking Advanced Customizations in Power BI with Deneb and VEGA Lite Power BI&amp;rsquo;s default Scatter Plot visual is robust but lacks some advanced customization features, such as the use of SVGs for better data representation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Six Sigma - Part One</title>
      <link>https://sageata.github.io/portfolio/blog/006-six-sigma-part-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 11:39:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sageata.github.io/portfolio/blog/006-six-sigma-part-one/</guid>
      <description>Abusing Excel: Streamlining Six Sigma Time Studies&amp;quot; In late 2022, I was tasked with preparing forms for Six Sigma time studies. Traditional methods involved pen and paper, followed by manual data entry into Excel—a laborious and error-prone process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Platform</title>
      <link>https://sageata.github.io/portfolio/blog/003-power-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 11:39:13 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sageata.github.io/portfolio/blog/003-power-app/</guid>
      <description>In December 2021, the Onboard Cabin Report (OCR) underwent a significant update. The categories were expanded to a five-level hierarchical taxonomy, allowing crew members to pre-classify the OCRs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automating the Onboard Cabin Report: A Machine Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://sageata.github.io/portfolio/blog/002-machine-learning-ocr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 11:39:10 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sageata.github.io/portfolio/blog/002-machine-learning-ocr/</guid>
      <description>Onboard Cabin Reports Classification using ML When I joined the Guest Delivery team, now known as Inflight Service &amp;amp; Hospitality, I quickly noticed an over-reliance on Excel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rediscovering My Passion for Coding: A Journey from Line Manager to Data Analyst</title>
      <link>https://sageata.github.io/portfolio/blog/001-line-manager-trends/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 11:17:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sageata.github.io/portfolio/blog/001-line-manager-trends/</guid>
      <description>Note that the data in the chart above is fictional
Although I graduated from an IT high school in 2001 with a focus on Junior Analysis and Programming, I didn&amp;rsquo;t fully immerse myself in the tech world until 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
